<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
  <MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>4.0</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>RoboSoft 4.0.802</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>http://robosoft.rudenko.com</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
  </MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
  <RoboSoft>
    <Company_UIN>CMP-005B0BB0661</Company_UIN>
    <Company_Description></Company_Description>
    <Product_UIN>APP-007519FEB0E</Product_UIN>
    <Search_String>AVS Audio Converter</Search_String>
    <Search_String_Unique>AVS Audio Converter</Search_String_Unique>
    <Publish_on_CD>FALSE</Publish_on_CD>
    <RSProductType></RSProductType>
    <Press_Release_Search_String></Press_Release_Search_String>
    <NewsFeed_Search_String></NewsFeed_Search_String>
    <Search_Engine_Search_String></Search_Engine_Search_String>
    <Web_Directories_Search_String></Web_Directories_Search_String>
    <Comments_For_Reviewer></Comments_For_Reviewer>
    <Backlink></Backlink>
  </RoboSoft>
  <Company_Info>
    <Company_Name>Ascensio System SIA</Company_Name>
    <Address_1>20A-6 Ernesta Birznieka-Upish street</Address_1>
    <Address_2></Address_2>
    <City_Town>Riga</City_Town>
    <State_Province></State_Province>
    <Zip_Postal_Code>LV-1050</Zip_Postal_Code>
    <Country>Latvia</Country>
    <Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.avs4you.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
    <Contact_Info>
      <Contact_First_Name>Irina</Contact_First_Name>
      <Contact_Last_Name>Sanaeva</Contact_Last_Name>
      <Contact_Email>submit@avs4you.com</Contact_Email>
      <Author_First_Name>Irina</Author_First_Name>
      <Author_Last_Name>Sanaeva</Author_Last_Name>
      <Author_Email>submit@avs4you.com</Author_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
    <Support_Info>
      <Sales_Email>submit@avs4you.com</Sales_Email>
      <Support_Email>submit@avs4you.com</Support_Email>
      <General_Email>submit@avs4you.com</General_Email>
      <Sales_Phone></Sales_Phone>
      <Support_Phone></Support_Phone>
      <General_Phone></General_Phone>
      <Fax_Phone></Fax_Phone>
    </Support_Info>
    <GooglePlusPage></GooglePlusPage>
    <LinkedinPage></LinkedinPage>
    <TwitterCompanyPage>https://twitter.com/avs4you</TwitterCompanyPage>
    <FacebookCompanyPage>https://www.facebook.com/avs4you</FacebookCompanyPage>
    <CompanyStorePage></CompanyStorePage>
  </Company_Info>
  <ASP>
    <ASP_FORM>Y</ASP_FORM>
    <ASP_Member>Y</ASP_Member>
    <ASP_Member_Number>06467</ASP_Member_Number>
  </ASP>
  <NewsFeed>
    <NewsFeed_FORM>Y</NewsFeed_FORM>
    <NewsFeed_VERSION>1.0</NewsFeed_VERSION>
    <NewsFeed_URL>http://Submit-Everywhere.com/extensions/NewsFeed.htm</NewsFeed_URL>
    <NewsFeed_DESCRIPTION>This PAD extension allows you to add your RSS and Atom news feeds info into your PAD file. This info can be used by RSS feed submission software or by feed directories themselves.</NewsFeed_DESCRIPTION>
    <NewsFeed_Type>RSS 0.90</NewsFeed_Type>
    <NewsFeed_Language>English</NewsFeed_Language>
    <NewsFeed_Purpose>News</NewsFeed_Purpose>
    <NewsFeed_Author_Email>submit@avs4you.com</NewsFeed_Author_Email>
    <NewsFeed_Author_First_Name>Irina</NewsFeed_Author_First_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Author_Last_Name>Sanaeva</NewsFeed_Author_Last_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Feed_URL></NewsFeed_Feed_URL>
    <NewsFeed_Site_Name></NewsFeed_Site_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Site_URL></NewsFeed_Site_URL>
    <NewsFeed_Title></NewsFeed_Title>
    <NewsFeed_Description_70></NewsFeed_Description_70>
    <NewsFeed_Description_250></NewsFeed_Description_250>
  </NewsFeed>
  <PAD_Certification_Promotion>
    <Apply_For_Certification>N</Apply_For_Certification>
  </PAD_Certification_Promotion>
  <Program_Info>
    <File_Info>
      <Automatically_Detect_File_Size>N</Automatically_Detect_File_Size>
      <File_Size_Bytes>51968208</File_Size_Bytes>
      <File_Size_K>50750</File_Size_K>
      <File_Size_MB>49.56</File_Size_MB>
      <Filename_Versioned></Filename_Versioned>
      <Filename_Previous></Filename_Previous>
      <Filename_Generic></Filename_Generic>
      <Filename_Long></Filename_Long>
    </File_Info>
    <Program_Target_Platform>Windows</Program_Target_Platform>
    <Program_Name>Free AVS Audio Converter</Program_Name>
    <Program_Version>10.4.1.636</Program_Version>
    <Program_Release_Month>05</Program_Release_Month>
    <Program_Release_Day>04</Program_Release_Day>
    <Program_Release_Year>2023</Program_Release_Year>
    <Program_Cost_Dollars>0</Program_Cost_Dollars>
    <Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type>
    <Program_Release_Status>New Release</Program_Release_Status>
    <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
    <Program_OS_Support>Win2000,WinXP,Win7 x32,Win7 x64,Windows 8,Windows 10,WinServer,WinOther,Windows2000,Windows2003,Windows Server 2000,Windows Server 2003,Windows Server 2008,Windows Server 2008r2,Windows Server 2012,Windows Tablet PC Edition 2005,Windows Media Center Edition 2005,WinVista,Windows Vista Starter,Windows Vista Home Basic,Windows Vista Home Premium,Windows Vista Business,Windows Vista Enterprise,Windows Vista Ultimate,WinVista x64,Windows Vista Home Basic x64,Windows Vista Home Premium x64,Windows Vista Business x64,Windows Vista Enterprise x64,Windows Vista Ultimate x64</Program_OS_Support>
    <Program_Language>English,Dutch,French,German,Italian,Japanese,Polish,Russian,Spanish</Program_Language>
    <Program_Change_Info>Import audio from MP4/MOV/M4V video files with Opus audio codec. Correct recognition of protected MP4/MOV/M4V video, M4A/M4B audio files. Correct M4A/M4B metatags creation. Open mirrored and rotated JPEG photos with the correct orientation on the cover. Critical vulnerabilities fix, optimization.</Program_Change_Info>
    <Program_System_Requirements>Intel/AMD compatible CPU at 1.86 GHz or higher, 1 GB RAM or higher, sound card, DirectX 9.0c or later</Program_System_Requirements>
    <Program_Category_Class>Audio &amp; Multimedia::Rippers &amp; Converters</Program_Category_Class>
    <Expire_Info>
      <Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
      <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
      <Expire_Count></Expire_Count>
      <Expire_Other_Info></Expire_Other_Info>
      <Expire_Month></Expire_Month>
      <Expire_Day></Expire_Day>
      <Expire_Year></Expire_Year>
    </Expire_Info>
    <Program_Categories>Rippers,Converters,Audio,Multimedia</Program_Categories>
    <Limitations>No limitations</Limitations>
    <Program_Cost_Other_Code></Program_Cost_Other_Code>
    <Program_Cost_Other></Program_Cost_Other>
    <Awards></Awards>
    <Program_Specific_Category></Program_Specific_Category>
    <Includes_JAVA_VM></Includes_JAVA_VM>
    <Includes_VB_Runtime></Includes_VB_Runtime>
    <Includes_DirectX></Includes_DirectX>
    <FacebookProductPage></FacebookProductPage>
    <GooglePlusProductPage></GooglePlusProductPage>
  </Program_Info>
  <Dynamic_PAD>
    <Dynamic_Distributive>N</Dynamic_Distributive>
  </Dynamic_PAD>
  <Web_Info>
    <Application_URLs>
      <Application_Info_URL>https://www.avs4you.com/avs-free-audio-converter.aspx</Application_Info_URL>
      <Application_Order_URL>https://www.avs4you.com/register.aspx</Application_Order_URL>
      <Application_Screenshot_URL>https://www.avs4you.com/pads/screenshots/avsaudioconverter.jpg</Application_Screenshot_URL>
      <Application_Icon_URL>https://www.avs4you.com/pads/icons/avsaudioconverter.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
      <Application_XML_File_URL>https://www.avs4you.com/pads/en/avsaudioconverter.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
    <Download_URLs>
      <Primary_Download_URL>https://download.avs4you.com/distributives/AVSAudioConverter.exe</Primary_Download_URL>
      <Secondary_Download_URL></Secondary_Download_URL>
      <Additional_Download_URL_1></Additional_Download_URL_1>
      <Additional_Download_URL_2></Additional_Download_URL_2>
    </Download_URLs>
  </Web_Info>
  <Permissions>
    <Distribution_Permissions>This product can be freely distributed through the Internet. To publish it on a CD, please contact info@avs4you.com.</Distribution_Permissions>
    <EULA>END-USER LICENSE AGREEMENT FOR SOFTWARE PRODUCTS OF ASCENSIO SYSTEM SIA

IMPORTANT-READ CAREFULLY: This End-User License Agreement is a legal Agreement between you and Ascensio System SIA for the applicable Software Products of Ascensio System SIA. Do not copy, install, or use the Software Products provided under this license agreement ('Agreement'), until you have carefully read the following terms and conditions.

Any reproduction or redistribution of Software Products or any of its components not in accordance with the End-User License Agreement is expressly prohibited by law, and may result in severe civil and criminal penalties.

Definitions: Software Products shall mean and include AVS4YOU Software.

AVS4YOU Software shall mean all of the contents of the files (provided either by electronic download, on physical media or any other method of distribution), disk(s), CD-ROM(s) or other media with which this Agreement is provided) which may be found at www.avs4you.com.

AVS4YOU Software is licensed on a per computer basis. Each license purchased is bound to one particular computer and allows using AVS4YOU Software on that single computer. If you install and use or reinstall AVS4YOU software on any other computers you will have to purchase an additional license for each computer. If you change a computer, you will have to purchase an additional license. All updates and upgrades for AVS4YOU Software are $0 for a user throughout the period of AVS4YOU license validity.

Your rights and obligations with respect to the use of AVS4YOU Software or any of its components are as follows.

You may

Install and use one copy of AVS4YOU Software or any of its components and all upgrades and updates on a single computer for any period for which you have purchased a subscription (typically 1 year or Unlimited).

Make one copy of AVS4YOU Software or any of its components for archival purposes on a storage device or media.

Use AVS4YOU Software on a network, provided that you have a licensed copy of AVS4YOU Software for each computer that can access AVS4YOU Software over that network for any period for which you have purchased a subscription (typically 1 year or Unlimited). A license for AVS4YOU Software may not be shared or used concurrently on different computers.A license for AVS4YOU Software may not be shared or used concurrently on different computers.

Receive support by e-mail to answer questions and solve problems referred to AVS4YOU Software for any period for which you have purchased a subscription (typically 1 year or Unlimited).

You may not

Use, copy, modify, or transfer copies of AVS4YOU Software except as provided for in this License.

Remove any proprietary notices or labels from AVS4YOU Software.

Reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble or make derivative works based on AVS4YOU Software (except and only to the extent that such activity is expressly permitted by applicable law notwithstanding this limitation).

Rent, lease, sublicense or assign AVS4YOU Software or any copy thereof, including any related documentation.

Separate AVS4YOU Software component parts for use on more than one computer.

Distribute the license key in any way.

Make any attempt to discover the source code of AVS4YOU Software.

NO WARRANTIES.

Ascensio System SIA expressly disclaims any warranty for AVS4YOU Software.

AVS4YOU SOFTWARE AND ANY RELATED DOCUMENTATION is PROVIDED 'AS IS' WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NONINFRINGEMENT.

THE ENTIRE RISK ARISING OUT OF USE OR PERFORMANCE OF AVS4YOU SOFTWARE REMAINS WITH YOU.

NO LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES.

IN NO EVENT SHALL ASCENSIO SYSTEM SIA BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION, OR ANY OTHER PECUNIARY LOSS) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR OF INABILITY TO USE AVS4YOU SOFTWARE.

COPYRIGHT NOTICE. Copyright © 2023 Ascensio System SIA, All rights reserved.

Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.</EULA>
  </Permissions>
  <AppStore>
    <AppStore_AppID></AppStore_AppID>
    <AppStore_Category></AppStore_Category>
    <AppStore_Info_URL></AppStore_Info_URL>
    <AppStore_Download_URL></AppStore_Download_URL>
    <AppStore_Promo_Code_1></AppStore_Promo_Code_1>
    <AppStore_Promo_Code_2></AppStore_Promo_Code_2>
    <AppStore_Promo_Code_3></AppStore_Promo_Code_3>
    <AppStore_Supported_Devices></AppStore_Supported_Devices>
    <AppStore_Other_Applications></AppStore_Other_Applications>
    <AppStore_Advantages_And_Unique_Features></AppStore_Advantages_And_Unique_Features>
    <AppStore_Awards_And_Ratings></AppStore_Awards_And_Ratings>
  </AppStore>
  <Program_Descriptions>
    <English>
      <Keywords>convert audio, mp4 to mp3, wav to mp3 converter, video to audio converter, m4a to mp3, music converter, ogg to mp3, audio converter, mp3 converter, wav converter, free audio converter, convert to mp3, audio file converter</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Convert all audio formats for free.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Convert all popular audio formats with Free AVS Audio Converter free and fast.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Convert audio between MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2 and other formats for free. Export and convert audio from your video files. Create ringtones for iPhone and make audiobooks. Use a command line mode for automatic conversion process.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Manage your music files efficiently with Free AVS Audio Converter. Convert MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2 and other popular audio formats for free. Automate routine work using ready conversion templates. Trim, delete parts, merge files, apply effects. Use batch conversion mode to convert a large number of audio files at once. Export audio from video files. Create individual ringtones for your iPhone and make simple audiobooks.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Convert all key audio formats, make basic edits, manage your audio collection, create ringtones for free. Enjoy fast audio conversion with Free AVS Audio Converter. Convert MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2, etc. for free. Manage APE files and encode them to any key audio format. 
Select and convert audio from your video files. Free AVS Audio Converter supports DVD, MPEG, MP4, AVI, DIVX, MOV, WMV, VOB, 3GP, RM, QT, FLV, etc. Support of H.265 (HEVC) and VP8/ VP9 video codecs. 
Use batch mode to convert and work with several files at one go. 
Edit audio before conversion. Trim, delete parts, merge files, apply effects. 
Modify extra text information in your audio files. Add your own data to audio files such as titles, authors, comments. 
Create audiobooks with AVS Audio Converter. Convert your audio tracks to M4B format, divide them into chapters, add bookmarks, set up quality level before audio conversion, prepare audio files for your iPod/iPhone. 
Create a unique ringtone for iPhone with AVS Audio Converter. Edit an audio file, save it to M4R format and upload to your smartphone. 
Automate routine work using ready conversion templates without clicking the program buttons manually. Create your own conversion patterns, set favourite presets and schedule an automatic conversion process. 
AVS4YOU tools let you easily convert and edit audio/video files, burn DVD/Blu-ray discs, create ringtones, upload videos to portable devices, players, phones and much more!</Char_Desc_2000>
    </English>
    <German>
      <Keywords>MP3, WMA, WAV, M4A, AMR, OGG, FLAC, MP2, APE, audio converter, mp3 music converter, audio ripper, mp3 umwandler, flac in mp3, cd mp3 converter, hörbuch erstellen, audiobook converter, m4b, klingelton iphone, audiodateien bearbeiten</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Konvertieren Sie Audios in mehrere Formate.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Konvertieren Sie gängige Audioformate mit AVS Audio Converter kostenlos.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Konvertieren Sie Audios in MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2 und andere Formate kostenlos. Exportieren Sie Audio aus Videos zum Konvertieren. Erstellen Sie Klingeltöne für iPhone und eigene Hörbücher. Verwenden Sie Kommandozeilen Modus.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Verwalten Sie Musikdateien effizient und kostenlos mit AVS Audio Converter. Konvertieren Sie MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2 und andere gängige Formate kostenlos. Automatisieren Sie die Konvertierung mit gebrauchsfertigen Vorlagen.  Schneiden, vereinigen Sie Audiodateien, löschen Sie einzelne Abschnitte, wenden Sie Effekte an. Exportieren/wandeln Sie Audio aus Videos um. Erstellen Sie Klingeltöne für iPhone und einfache Hörbücher.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Konvertieren Sie gängige Audioformate, nutzen Sie grundlegende Bearbeitungstools, verwalten Sie Ihre Sammlung von Audios, erstellen Sie Klingeltöne kostenlos. Wandeln Sie Audios schneller und kostenlos mit AVS Audio Converter um. Konvertieren Sie MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2, usw. kostenlos. Verwalten Sie APE-Dateien und kodieren Sie diese in jedes Audioformat.
Wählen und konvertieren Sie Audiospuren aus Ihren Videodateien. Kostenloser AVS Audio Converter unterstützt DVD, MPEG, MP4, AVI, DIVX, MOV, WMV, VOB, 3GP, RM, QT, FLV usw. 
Nutzen Sie den Stampelmodus, um mehrere Dateien auf einmal zu verarbeiten.
Bearbeiten Sie Audios vor der Konvertierung. Schneiden und löschen Sie Abschnitte, vereinigen Sie Dateien und wenden Sie Effekte an.
Ändern Sie zusätzliche Textinformationen in Ihren Audiodateien. Fügen Sie Titel, Autoren, Kommentare und andere Daten hinzu.
Erstellen Sie Hörbücher: wandeln Sie Ihre Audiotracks ins gängige M4B-Format um, teilen Sie diese in Kapitel auf und fügen Sie Lesezeichen hinzu. Bestimmen Sie die Qualität der Ausgabeaudiodatei vor der Umwandlung. Bereiten Sie Ihre Audiodateien für Ihren iPod bzw. Ihr iPhone vor. 
Mit AVS Audio Converter können Sie Klingeltöne für iPhone erstellen: bearbeiten Sie eine Audiodatei und speichern Sie diese ins M4R-Format für Ihr Smartphone. 
Schneiden und vereinigen Sie Audiodateien, löschen Sie einzelne Abschnitte, wenden Sie Effekte an, ändern Sie zusätzliche Textinformationen. 
Automatisieren Sie die Konvertierung mit gebrauchsfertigen Konvertierungsvorlagen, sodass Sie jedes Mal auf Schaltflächen nicht klicken müssen. Erstellen Sie Ihre eigenen Konvertierungsparameter, nutzen Sie Ihre bevorzugten Voreinstellungen und planen Sie automatische Konvertierung ein.
Die AVS4YOU-Programme ermöglichen Ihnen Audio- und Videodateien einfach zu rippen, zu konvertieren und zu bearbeiten, DVDs zu brennen, Klingeltöne zu erstellen, Videos auf tragbare Geräte, Player sowie Mobiltelefone zu übertragen und vieles.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </German>
    <French>
      <Keywords>convertisseur audio, convertisseur musique, convertir audio en mp3,convertisseur mp3, audio mp3, convertisseur musique en mp3, extraire audio, convertisseur cda, cd audio, format MP3,WMA,WAV,M4A,AMR,OGG,FLAC, créez livres audio, sonnerie pour iPhone</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Traitez les formats audio!</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Convertissez les audios des tous les formats avec AVS Audio Converter gratuit.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Convertissez gratuitement des formats audio MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2. Extrayez, convertissez l'audio à partir des vidéos. Créez des sonneries pour iPhone et des livres audio. Automatisez la conversion via la ligne de commande.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Gérez vos fichiers avec AVS Audio Converter gratuit. Convertissez gratuitement les formats : MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2. Automatiser le travail en utilisant les modèles de conversion. Découpez, supprimez des parties, fusionnez des fichiers, appliquez des effets. Convertissez plusieurs fichiers en même temps. Extrayez l'audio des vidéos. Créez des sonneries pour iPhone et des livres audio simples.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Convertissez tous les formats audio populaires, éditez, gérez vos fichiers, créez des sonneries. Profitez de la conversion rapide avec AVS Audio Converter gratuit. Convertissez gratuitement MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2, etc. Gérez les fichiers APE et décodez-les aux formats audio courants.
Sélectionnez et convertissez l'audio à partir des fichiers vidéo. Le logiciel prend en charge DVD, MPEG, MP4, AVI, DIVX, MOV, WMV, VOB, 3GP, RM, QT, FLV, etc. 
Utilisez le mode de traitement par lots pour convertir et traiter plusieurs fichiers en une seule fois. 
Éditez l'audio avant la conversion. Découpez, supprimez les parties, fusionnez des fichiers, appliquez des effets. 
Modifiez des informations textuelles de vos fichiers audio. Ajoutez vos données : titre, auteur, commentaires. 
Convertissez des pistes audio au format M4B avec AVS Audio Converter. Divisez les pistes en parties et ajoutez des signets. Définissez le niveau de qualité avant de convertir. 
Créez les fichiers audio pour votre iPod/iPhone. Ajoutez vos propres informations aux fichiers audio (titres, auteurs, commentaires). 
Éditez un fichier audio et enregistrez-le au format M4P pour iPhone. Créez une sonnerie individuelle avec AVS Audio Converter. 
La ligne de commande permet d'automatiser votre travail de routine à l'aide des modèles de conversion sans avoir cliqué sur les boutons manuellement. 
Les logiciels AVS4YOU vous permettent d'extraire, de convertir et d'éditer facilement des fichiers audio/vidéo, de graver DVD, de créer des sonneries, de télécharger des vidéos sur les appareils portables, lecteurs, téléphones et encore plus !</Char_Desc_2000>
    </French>
    <Russian>
      <Keywords>аудио конвертер, конвертировать в mp3, конвертер музыки, mp3 конвертер, MP3, WMA, WAV, M4A, AMR, OGG, FLAC, рингтон для iphone</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Конвертируйте все аудио форматы бесплатно!</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Конвертируйте все популярные аудио форматы в  Free AVS Audio Converter  беслатно</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Конвертируйте файлы в форматах MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG и др. Извлекайте и конвертируйте звуковые дорожки из своих видеофайлов. Создавайте рингтоны и аудиокниги. Используйте режим командной строки для автоматизации процесса конвертации</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Конвертируйте файлы в форматах MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2 и др бесплатно с помощью Free AVS Audio Converter. Автоматизируйте рутинную работу, используя готовые шаблоны конвертации. Обрезайте, удаляйте части, объединяйте файлы, применяйте эффекты. Используйте пакетный режим конвертации для преобразования и работы с несколькими файлами одновременно. Создавайте уникальные рингтоны и аудиокниги для прослушивания на iPod/iPhone.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Конвертируйте все ключевые аудио форматы, вносите основные изменения, управляйте своей аудио коллекцией, создавайте рингтоны бесплатно. Наслаждайтесь быстрым преобразованием звука с помощью бесплатного AVS Audio Converter. Конвертируйте MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2 и т. д. бесплатно. Управляйте файлами APE и кодируйте их в любой ключевой аудиоформат.
Извлекайте и конвертируйте звуковые дорожки из своих видеофайлов. Free AVS Audio Converter поддерживает форматы DVD, MPEG, MP4, AVI, DIVX, MOV, WMV, VOB, 3GP, RM, QT, FLV и другие. Поддержка H.265 (HEVC) и VP8/ VP9 видео кодеков. 
Используйте пакетный режим конвертации для преобразования и работы с несколькими файлами одновременно. 
Вы можете отредактировать аудио перед конвертацией: обрезать, удалить отдельные части, объединить файлы, наложить эффекты, изменить дополнительную текстовую информацию в аудиофайлах. Вы можете добавить такие данные в аудио файлы, как названия, авторов, комментарии. 
Создавайте аудиокниги с помощью AVS Audio Converter: конвертируйте аудиофайлы в формат M4B, разделяйте их на главы и добавляйте закладки, подготовьте аудиофайлы для прослушивания на iPod/iPhone. 
Создавайте рингтон для iPhone с AVS Audio Converter: отредактируйте аудиофайл и сохраните его в формат M4R для iPhone, создайте свой собственный оригинальный рингтон. 
С помощью AVS Audio Converter Вы можете автоматизировать рутинную работу, используя режим командной строки. Используйте готовые шаблоны конвертации без необходимости нажатия кнопок программы вручную. Это поможет ускорить процесс преобразования Ваших файлов. 
AVS4YOU продукты позволяют легко конвертировать и редактировать аудио/видео файлы, редактировать изображения, записывать DVD, создавать рингтоны, загружать видео на портативные устройства, плееры, телефоны и многое другое!</Char_Desc_2000>
    </Russian>
    <Spanish>
      <Keywords>convertir audio, convertir música, convertir archivos a mp3, convertidor mp3, mp3 audio, convertir música a mp3, grabadora de audio, audio cd, formato mp3, MP3, WMA, WAV, M4A, AMR, OGG, FLAC, crear audiolibros, tono de llamada para Iphone</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Convierta archivos de audio gratis.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Convierta todos los formatos de audio con Free AVS Audio Converter gratis.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Convierta archivos de audio MP3, WMA, WAV, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2, etc. gratis. Exporte y convierta audio de sus archivos de vídeo. Cree tonos de llamada y audiolibros para iPhone. Utilice modo de línea de comandos para conversión automática.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Administre archivos de música eficientemente con Free AVS Audio Converter. Convierta MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2 y otros formatos de audio gratis. Automatice trabajo de rutina utilizando plantillas listas. Recorte, elimine partes, fusione archivos, aplique efectos.Use el modo de conversión por lotes para convertir una gran cantidad de archivos de audio a la vez. Cree tonos de llamada individuales y haga audiolibros.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Convierta todos los formatos de audio clave, realice ediciones básicas, gestione su colección de audio, cree tonos de llamada gratis. Disfruta de una rápida conversión de audio con Free AVS Audio Converter. Convierta archivos MP3, WAV, WMA, AMR, AAC, M4A, FLAC, OGG, MP2, etc gratis. Administre archivos APE y codifíquelos a cualquier formato de audio compatible con AVS Audio Converter. 
Seleccione y convierte audio de sus archivos de vídeo. Free AVS Audio Converter soporta DVD, MPEG, MP4, AVI, DIVX, MOV, WMV, VOB, 3GP, RM, QT, FLV, etc. Soporte de códecs de video H.265 (HEVC) y VP8 / VP9. 
Utilice el modo por lotes para convertir y trabajar con varios archivos a la vez. 
Edite audio antes de conversión. Recorte, elimine partes, fusione archivos, aplique efectos. 
Modifique la información de texto adicional en sus archivos de audio. Agregue sus propios datos a archivos de audio tales como títulos, autores, comentarios. 
Convierta sus pistas de audio al formato M4B con AVS Audio Converter: divídalos en capítulos y agregue marcadores, configure el nivel de calidad antes de la conversión de audio, prepare archivos de audio para su iPod / iPhone. 
Edite archivo de audio y guárdelo en formato M4R para iPhone. Haga un tono de llamada individual con AVS Audio Converter. 
Automatice el trabajo de rutina utilizando plantillas de conversión listas sin hacer clic en los botones del programa manualmente. Cree sus propios plantillasde conversión, establezca preajustes favoritos y programe un proceso de conversión automático. 
Las herramientas AVS4YOU le permiten extraer, convertir y editar fácilmente archivos de audio / vídeo, grabar DVDs, crear tonos de llamada, subir vídeos a dispositivos portátiles, reproductores, teléfonos y mucho más.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </Spanish>
  </Program_Descriptions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
