<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
  <MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>4.0</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>RoboSoft 4.0.797</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>http://robosoft.rudenko.com</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
    <CERTIFIED>N</CERTIFIED>
  </MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
  <RoboSoft>
    <Company_UIN>CMP-005B0BB0661</Company_UIN>
    <Company_Description></Company_Description>
    <Product_UIN>APP-00850F35B87</Product_UIN>
    <Search_String>Free AVS Video Converter</Search_String>
    <Search_String_Unique>Free AVS Video Converter</Search_String_Unique>
    <Publish_on_CD>FALSE</Publish_on_CD>
    <RSProductType></RSProductType>
    <Press_Release_Search_String></Press_Release_Search_String>
    <NewsFeed_Search_String></NewsFeed_Search_String>
    <Search_Engine_Search_String></Search_Engine_Search_String>
    <Web_Directories_Search_String></Web_Directories_Search_String>
    <Comments_For_Reviewer></Comments_For_Reviewer>
    <Backlink></Backlink>
  </RoboSoft>
  <Company_Info>
    <Company_Name>Online Media Technologies Ltd., UK</Company_Name>
    <Address_1>Suite 12, 2nd Floor, Queens House</Address_1>
    <Address_2>180 Tottenham Court Road</Address_2>
    <City_Town>London</City_Town>
    <State_Province></State_Province>
    <Zip_Postal_Code>W1T 7PD</Zip_Postal_Code>
    <Country>United Kingdom</Country>
    <Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.avs4you.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
    <Contact_Info>
      <Contact_First_Name>Irina</Contact_First_Name>
      <Contact_Last_Name>Sanaeva</Contact_Last_Name>
      <Contact_Email>submit@avs4you.com</Contact_Email>
      <Author_First_Name>Irina</Author_First_Name>
      <Author_Last_Name>Sanaeva</Author_Last_Name>
      <Author_Email>submit@avs4you.com</Author_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
    <Support_Info>
      <Sales_Email>submit@avs4you.com</Sales_Email>
      <Support_Email>submit@avs4you.com</Support_Email>
      <General_Email>submit@avs4you.com</General_Email>
      <Sales_Phone></Sales_Phone>
      <Support_Phone></Support_Phone>
      <General_Phone></General_Phone>
      <Fax_Phone></Fax_Phone>
    </Support_Info>
    <GooglePlusPage></GooglePlusPage>
    <LinkedinPage></LinkedinPage>
    <TwitterCompanyPage>https://twitter.com/avs4you</TwitterCompanyPage>
    <FacebookCompanyPage>https://www.facebook.com/avs4you</FacebookCompanyPage>
    <CompanyStorePage></CompanyStorePage>
    <PublisherID>pid-3800119d2d51</PublisherID>
    <BrandID>bid-79007e1bd361</BrandID>
  </Company_Info>
  <ASP>
    <ASP_FORM>Y</ASP_FORM>
    <ASP_Member>Y</ASP_Member>
    <ASP_Member_Number>06467</ASP_Member_Number>
  </ASP>
  <NewsFeed>
    <NewsFeed_FORM>Y</NewsFeed_FORM>
    <NewsFeed_VERSION>1.0</NewsFeed_VERSION>
    <NewsFeed_URL>http://Submit-Everywhere.com/extensions/NewsFeed.htm</NewsFeed_URL>
    <NewsFeed_DESCRIPTION>This PAD extension allows you to add your RSS and Atom news feeds info into your PAD file. This info can be used by RSS feed submission software or by feed directories themselves.</NewsFeed_DESCRIPTION>
    <NewsFeed_Type>RSS 0.90</NewsFeed_Type>
    <NewsFeed_Author_First_Name>Irina</NewsFeed_Author_First_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Author_Last_Name>Sanaeva</NewsFeed_Author_Last_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Author_Email>submit@avs4you.com</NewsFeed_Author_Email>
    <NewsFeed_Language>English</NewsFeed_Language>
    <NewsFeed_Purpose>News</NewsFeed_Purpose>
    <NewsFeed_Feed_URL></NewsFeed_Feed_URL>
    <NewsFeed_Site_Name></NewsFeed_Site_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Site_URL></NewsFeed_Site_URL>
    <NewsFeed_Title></NewsFeed_Title>
    <NewsFeed_Description_70></NewsFeed_Description_70>
    <NewsFeed_Description_250></NewsFeed_Description_250>
  </NewsFeed>
  <PAD_Certification_Promotion>
    <Apply_For_Certification>N</Apply_For_Certification>
  </PAD_Certification_Promotion>
  <Program_Info>
    <AppID>app-210023cfff7a</AppID>
    <Program_Target_Platform>Windows</Program_Target_Platform>
    <File_Info>
      <Automatically_Detect_File_Size>N</Automatically_Detect_File_Size>
      <File_Size_Bytes>84916992</File_Size_Bytes>
      <File_Size_K>82926</File_Size_K>
      <File_Size_MB>80.98</File_Size_MB>
      <Filename_Versioned></Filename_Versioned>
      <Filename_Previous></Filename_Previous>
      <Filename_Generic></Filename_Generic>
      <Filename_Long></Filename_Long>
    </File_Info>
    <Program_Name>Free AVS Video Converter</Program_Name>
    <Program_Version>12.2.1.684</Program_Version>
    <Program_Release_Month>08</Program_Release_Month>
    <Program_Release_Day>05</Program_Release_Day>
    <Program_Release_Year>2021</Program_Release_Year>
    <Program_Cost_Dollars>0</Program_Cost_Dollars>
    <Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type>
    <Program_Release_Status>New Release</Program_Release_Status>
    <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
    <Program_OS_Support>Win2000,WinXP,Win7 x32,Win7 x64,Windows 8,Windows 10,WinServer,WinOther,Windows2000,Windows2003,Windows Server 2000,Windows Server 2003,Windows Server 2008,Windows Server 2008r2,Windows Server 2012,Windows Tablet PC Edition 2005,Windows Media Center Edition 2005,WinVista,Windows Vista Starter,Windows Vista Home Basic,Windows Vista Home Premium,Windows Vista Business,Windows Vista Enterprise,Windows Vista Ultimate,WinVista x64,Windows Vista Home Basic x64,Windows Vista Home Premium x64,Windows Vista Business x64,Windows Vista Enterprise x64,Windows Vista Ultimate x64</Program_OS_Support>
    <Program_Language>English,Danish,Dutch,French,German,Italian,Japanese,Korean,Polish,Portuguese,Russian,Spanish</Program_Language>
    <Program_Change_Info>Support of OPUS audio in MKV, MKA, WEBM, WEBA files. New slideshow presets for MOV and MKV. New video effects - Bezier Curve, Curved Arrow. Enhanced support of AVI, MKV and WEBM files. Support of HEIF/HEIC images in disc menu. Enhanced usability and accessibility. Optimization and bug fixes.</Program_Change_Info>
    <Program_System_Requirements>AMD/Intel Core 2 Duo compatible CPU at 3 GHz, 2 GB RAM, sound card, DirectX 9.0c</Program_System_Requirements>
    <Program_Category_Class>Audio &amp; Multimedia::Video Tools</Program_Category_Class>
    <Expire_Info>
      <Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
      <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
      <Expire_Count></Expire_Count>
      <Expire_Other_Info></Expire_Other_Info>
      <Expire_Month></Expire_Month>
      <Expire_Day></Expire_Day>
      <Expire_Year></Expire_Year>
    </Expire_Info>
    <Program_Categories>Multimedia and Design :: Video Editors,Multimedia and Design :: Converters</Program_Categories>
    <Limitations>No limitations</Limitations>
    <Program_Cost_Other_Code></Program_Cost_Other_Code>
    <Program_Cost_Other></Program_Cost_Other>
    <Awards></Awards>
    <Program_Specific_Category></Program_Specific_Category>
    <Includes_JAVA_VM></Includes_JAVA_VM>
    <Includes_VB_Runtime></Includes_VB_Runtime>
    <Includes_DirectX></Includes_DirectX>
    <FacebookProductPage></FacebookProductPage>
    <GooglePlusProductPage></GooglePlusProductPage>
  </Program_Info>
  <Dynamic_PAD>
    <Dynamic_Distributive>N</Dynamic_Distributive>
    <General>
      <DP_Pad_Enabled>TRUE</DP_Pad_Enabled>
      <DP_AtFormFill_Enabled>TRUE</DP_AtFormFill_Enabled>
      <DP_Distributive_Enabled>FALSE</DP_Distributive_Enabled>
      <DP_Script_Base_URL>http://repository.appvisor.com/</DP_Script_Base_URL>
      <DP_Pad_Mask>AVSVideoConverter.xml</DP_Pad_Mask>
      <DP_Distributive_Primary_URL>http://download.avs4you.com/distributives/AVSVideoConverter.exe</DP_Distributive_Primary_URL>
      <DP_Distributive_Mask>AVSVideoConverter.exe</DP_Distributive_Mask>
    </General>
  </Dynamic_PAD>
  <Web_Info>
    <Application_URLs>
      <Application_Info_URL>https://www.avs4you.com/avs-free-video-converter.aspx</Application_Info_URL>
      <Application_Order_URL>https://www.avs4you.com/register.aspx</Application_Order_URL>
      <Application_Screenshot_URL>https://www.avs4you.com/pads/screenshots/avsvideoconverter.jpg</Application_Screenshot_URL>
      <Application_Icon_URL>http://www.avs4you.com/pads/icons/avsvideoconverter.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
      <Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.avs4you.com/pads/en/avsvideoconverter.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
    <Download_URLs>
      <Primary_Download_URL>http://download.avs4you.com/distributives/AVSVideoConverter.exe</Primary_Download_URL>
      <Secondary_Download_URL></Secondary_Download_URL>
      <Additional_Download_URL_1></Additional_Download_URL_1>
      <Additional_Download_URL_2></Additional_Download_URL_2>
    </Download_URLs>
  </Web_Info>
  <Permissions>
    <Distribution_Permissions>This product can be freely distributed through the Internet. To publish it on a CD, please contact info@avs4you.com</Distribution_Permissions>
    <EULA>END-USER LICENSE AGREEMENT FOR SOFTWARE PRODUCTS OF ONLINE MEDIA TECHNOLOGIES LTD.

IMPORTANT-READ CAREFULLY: This End-User License Agreement is a legal Agreement between you and Online Media Technologies Ltd for the applicable Software Products of Online Media Technologies Ltd. Do not copy, install, or use the Software Products provided under this license agreement ("Agreement"), until you have carefully read the following terms and conditions.

Any reproduction or redistribution of Software Products or any of its components not in accordance with the End-User License Agreement is expressly prohibited by law, and may result in severe civil and criminal penalties. 

Definitions: Software Products shall mean and include AVS4YOU Software. 

AVS4YOU Software shall mean all of the contents of the files (provided either by electronic download, on physical media or any other method of distribution), disk(s), CD-ROM(s) or other media with which this Agreement is provided) which may be found at www.avs4you.com. 

AVS4YOU Software is licensed on a per computer basis. Each license purchased is bound to one particular computer and allows using AVS4YOU Software on that single computer. If you install and use or reinstall AVS4YOU software on any other computers you will have to purchase an additional license for each computer. If you change a computer, you will have to purchase an additional license. All updates and upgrades for AVS4YOU Software are free for a user throughout the period of AVS4YOU license validity. 

Your rights and obligations with respect to the use of AVS4YOU Software or any of its components are as follows: 

You may: 
1. Install and use one copy of AVS4YOU Software or any of its components and all upgrades and updates on a single computer for any period for which you have purchased a subscription (typically 1 year or Unlimited). 
2. Make one copy of AVS4YOU Software or any of its components for archival purposes on a storage device or media. 
3. Use AVS4YOU Software on a network, provided that you have a licensed copy of AVS4YOU Software for each computer that can access AVS4YOU Software over that network for any period for which you have purchased a subscription (typically 1 year or Unlimited). A license for AVS4YOU Software may not be shared or used concurrently on different computers. 
4. Receive support by e-mail to answer questions and solve problems referred to AVS4YOU Software for any period for which you have purchased a subscription (typically 1 year or Unlimited). 

You may not: 
1. Use, copy, modify, or transfer copies of AVS4YOU Software except as provided for in this License. 
2. Remove any proprietary notices or labels from AVS4YOU Software. 
3. Reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble or make derivative works based on AVS4YOU Software (except and only to the extent that such activity is expressly permitted by applicable law notwithstanding this limitation). 
4. Rent, lease, sublicense or assign AVS4YOU Software or any copy thereof, including any related documentation. 
5. Separate AVS4YOU Software component parts for use on more than one computer. 
6. Distribute the license key in any way. 
7. Make any attempt to discover the source code of AVS4YOU Software. 


NO WARRANTIES. 

Online Media Technologies Ltd. expressly disclaims any warranty for AVS4YOU Software. 

AVS4YOU SOFTWARE AND ANY RELATED DOCUMENTATION is PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NONINFRINGEMENT. 

THE ENTIRE RISK ARISING OUT OF USE OR PERFORMANCE OF AVS4YOU SOFTWARE REMAINS WITH YOU. 

NO LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. 
IN NO EVENT SHALL ONLINE MEDIA TECHNOLOGIES LTD BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION, OR ANY OTHER PECUNIARY LOSS) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR OF INABILITY TO USE AVS4YOU SOFTWARE. 

COPYRIGHT NOTICE. Copyright(C) 2020 Online Media Technologies Ltd. All rights reserved. 
Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.</EULA>
  </Permissions>
  <AppStore>
    <AppStore_AppID></AppStore_AppID>
    <AppStore_Category></AppStore_Category>
    <AppStore_Info_URL></AppStore_Info_URL>
    <AppStore_Download_URL></AppStore_Download_URL>
    <AppStore_Promo_Code_1></AppStore_Promo_Code_1>
    <AppStore_Promo_Code_2></AppStore_Promo_Code_2>
    <AppStore_Promo_Code_3></AppStore_Promo_Code_3>
    <AppStore_Supported_Devices></AppStore_Supported_Devices>
    <AppStore_Other_Applications></AppStore_Other_Applications>
    <AppStore_Advantages_And_Unique_Features></AppStore_Advantages_And_Unique_Features>
    <AppStore_Awards_And_Ratings></AppStore_Awards_And_Ratings>
  </AppStore>
  <Program_Descriptions>
    <English>
      <Keywords>video converter, free video converter, convert video, mp4 converter, video converter download, best free video converter, video converter to mp4, video to audio converter, youtube video converter, convert video to gif, video to audio converter</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Convert all video formats for free.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Convert all popular video formats with Free AVS Video Converter free and fast.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Convert video to all key video formats and for all popular devices with Free AVS Video Converter. Convert MP4 DVD AVI MPEG VOB MOV WMV M4V HDV free and fast. Speed up video conversion due to GPU acceleration. Export audio from video.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Convert video between all formats with Free AVS Video Converter absolutely for free: MP4, DVD, MPEG, VOB, 2K QHD, 4K UHD, MOV, AVI, WMV, MKV, FLV, TS, Blu-ray, etc. Use smart presets to convert video for iPhone, iPad, Samsung, Android tablets,phablets, smart TV and smartphones. Use batch conversion mode to convert a large number of files at once. Correct aspect ratio. Export audio from video. Burn video to DVD/Blu-ray discs with a menu.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Convert video between all key formats with Free AVS Video Converter absolutely for free: MP4, DVD, MPEG, VOB, 2K QHD, 4K UHD, MOV, AVI, WMV, MKV, FLV, TS, Blu-ray, etc. Use smart presets to convert video for iPhone, iPad, Samsung, Android tablets,phablets, smart TV and smartphones. 
Free AVS Video Converter allows you to convert HD, Full HD, 2K Quad HD, 4K Ultra HD and DCI 4K video using ultra new presets and enjoy high quality video playback. 
Convert video files including MKV with subtitles easily and fast. 
Free AVS Video Converter can speed up video conversion in several ways. You can convert a large number of video files at once choosing batch conversion or command-line modes. Command-line mode helps to automate and schedule conversion that is extremely useful for routine work. 
Use hardware acceleration for video decoding by means of video cards (GPU): Intel HD Graphics (Intel Quick Sync Video technology) or NVIDIA GeForce (NVIDIA CUDA platform). These technologies help to playback and convert Full HD video with a high bitrate or 2K QHD and 4K UHD faster. 
Make basic edits before converting video: correct aspect ratio, crop scale, split videos by size or chapters, export audio and images from video, add various video, audio and text effects. Play with new effects such as arrows, Tilt-shift, particles, countdown, etc. 
Convert video for YouTube free and fast, select a necessary preset depending on the desired quality of the output file. Free AVS Video Converter also converts video for Facebook and popular video hosting websites such as Vimeo, Daily Motion, Telly. Burn DVD/Blu-ray discs with stylish menus.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </English>
    <French>
      <Keywords>video converter, free video converter, convertisseur video, convertisseur video gratuit, convertisseur video youtube, logiciel convertisseur video, convertisseur video mp4, convertisseur vidéo gratuit, convertir video, convertir video youtube</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Convertissez tous formats vidéo gratuitement</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Convertissez tous les formats vidéo avec AVS Video Converter vite et gratuitem</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Convertissez vidéo dans tous formats pour tous les appareils avec Free AVS Video Converter. Convertissez MP4 DVD AVI MPEG VOB MOV WMV M4V HDV vite et gratuitement. Accélérez conversion vidéo grâce a l'accélération GPU. Exportez audio depuis vidéo.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Convertissez vidéo entre tous les formats avec Free AVS Video Converter gratuitement: MP4, DVD, MPEG, VOB, 2K QHD, 4K UHD, MOV, AVI, WMV, MKV, FLV, TS, Blu-ray, etc. Profitez de presets intelligents pour convertir vidéo pour iPhone, iPad, Samsung, tablettes Android, phablettes, téléviseurs intelligents et smartphones.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Convertissez vidéo entre tous les formats avec Free AVS Video Converter gratuitement: MP4, DVD, MPEG, VOB, 2K QHD, 4K UHD, MOV, AVI, WMV, MKV, FLV, TS, Blu-ray, etc. Profitez de presets intelligents pour convertir vidéo pour iPhone, iPad, Samsung, tablettes Android, phablettes, téléviseurs intelligents et smartphones. 
Free AVS Video Converter vous permet de convertir HD, Full HD, 2K Quad HD, 4K Ultra HD et DCI 4K vidéo en utilisant des nouveaux presets et profiter de vidéos de haute qualité. 
Convertissez fichiers vidéo y compris MKV avec sous-titres vite et facilement. 
Free AVS Video Converter peut accélérer la conversion de vos vidéos de plusieurs façons. Vous pouvez convertir un grand nombre de fichiers vidéo à la fois avec la conversion en batch ou mode ligne de commande. Mode ligne de commande permet d'automatiser et programmer la conversion ce qui est très utile pour le travail de routine. 
Utilisez l'accélération matérielle pour le décodage vidéo au moyen de cartes vidéo (GPU): Intel HD Graphics (Intel® Quick Sync Video technology) ou NVIDIA® GeForce® (NVIDIA CUDA® platform). Ces technologies aident à convertir et reproduire vidéo Full HD avec un débit binaire élevé ou 2K QHD et 4K UHD plus vite. 
Faites des corrections basiques avant convertir vidéo: changer le rapport d'aspect, utiliser recadrage, diviser vidéo selon la taille ou par chapitres, exporter audio et images depuis vidéo, ajouter différents effets vidéo, audio et texte. Jouez avec des nouveaux effets tels comme flèches, tête inclinable, particules, compte à rebours, etc. 
Convertissez vidéo pour YouTube gratuitement et vite, choisissez presets nécessaires selon la qualité souhaitée du fichier de sortie. Free AVS Video Converter convertit vidéo pour Facebook et d'autres site d'hébergement de vidéos comme Vimeo, Daily Motion, Telly. Gravez disques DVD/Blu-ray avec menus de style.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </French>
    <German>
      <Keywords>video converter, free video converter, youtube video converter, facebook video converter, video to audio converter, video konvertieren, kostenloser video converter</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Konvertieren Sie alle Videoformate kostenlos</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Konvertieren Sie Videos kostenlos mit Free AVS Video Converter.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Konvertieren Sie Videos in alle gängigen Videoformate und für alle beliebten Geräte Mit Free AVS Video Converter. Konvertieren Sie MP4 DVD AVI MPEG VOB MOV WMV M4V HDV kostenlos und schnell. Beschleunigen Sie Videoumwandlung mit GPU.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Konvertieren Sie Videos zwischen allen Formaten mit Free AVS Video Converter absolut kostenlos: MP4, DVD, MPEG, VOB, 2K QHD, 4K UHD, MOV, AVI, WMV, MKV, FLV, TS, Blu-ray, usw. Verwenden Sie fertige Voreinstellungen für die Konvertierung der Videos für iPhone, iPad, Samsung, Android-Tablets, Smart-TV und Smartphones. Verwenden Sie Stapelmodus, um eine große Anzahl von Dateien auf einmal zu konvertieren. Passen Sie Seitenverhältnis an.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Konvertieren Sie Videos zwischen allen gängigen Formaten mit Free AVS Video Converter absolut kostenlos: MP4, DVD, MPEG, VOB, 2K QHD, 4K UHD, MOV, AVI, WMV, MKV, FLV, TS, Blu-ray, etc. Verwenden Sie fertige Voreinstellungen für die Konvertierung der Videos für iPhone, iPad, Samsung, Android-Tablets, Smart-TV und Smartphones. 
Free AVS Video Converter ermöglicht es Ihnen, HD, Full HD, 2K Quad HD, 4K Ultra HD und DCI 4K Video mit ultra neuen Voreinstellungen zu konvertieren und hochwertige Video-Wiedergabe zu genießen. 
Konvertieren Sie Videodateien einschließlich MKV mit Untertiteln einfach und schnell. 
Free AVS Video Converter kann Videoumwandlung auf verschiedene Arten beschleunigen. Sie können eine große Anzahl von Videodateien mit der Hilfe von Stapelmodus oder Kommandozeilen Modus auf einmal konvertieren. 
Kommandozeilenmodus hilft, die Konvertierung zu automatisieren und zu planen, die für Routineaufgaben äußerst nützlich ist. 
Verwenden Sie Hardwarebeschleunigung für die Video-Dekodierung mittels Grafikkarten (GPU): Intel HD-Grafik (Intel Quick Sync Video Technologie) oder NVIDIA GeForce (NVIDIA CUDA Plattform). Diese Technologien helfen, Full-HD-Video mit einer großen Bitrate oder 2K QHD und 4K UHD schneller zu spielen und zu konvertieren. 
Nehmen Sie vor der Videoumwandlung grundlegende Änderungen vor: passen Sie Seitenverhältnis an, teilen Sie Videos nach Größe oder Kapiteln auf, exportieren Sie den Ton aus Videodatei, fügen Sie verschiedene Video -, Audio-und Texteffekte hinzu. 
Konvertieren Sie Video für YouTube kostenlos und schnell, wählen Sie ein notwendiges Preset abhängig von der gewünschten Qualität der Ausgabedatei. Free AVS Video Converter konvertiert auch video für Facebook, Vimeo, Daily Motion, Telly. Brennen Sie DVD - /Blu-ray-Вiscs mit stilvollen Menüs.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </German>
    <Russian>
      <Keywords>видео конвертер, бесплатный видео конвертер, конвертировать видео, MP4 конвертер, видео конвертер скачать, лучший бесплатный видео конвертер, видео конвертер в MP4, видео в аудио конвертер, YouTube конвертер видео, конвертировать видео в GIF</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Конвертируйте все видео форматы бесплатно.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Конвертируйте все популярные форматы видео с помощью Free AVS Video Converter</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Конвертируйте видео во все ключевые форматы видео и для всех популярных устройств с помощью Free AVS Video Converter. Конвертировать MP4 DVD AVI MPEG VOB MOV бесплатно и быстро. Ускорьте конвертацию видео за счет ускорения графического процессора.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Конвертируйте видео во все форматы с помощью бесплатного AVS Video Converter абсолютно бесплатно: MP4, DVD, MPEG, VOB, 2K QHD, 4K UHD, MOV, AVI, WMV, MKV, FLV, TS, Blu-ray и т. Д. Используйте умные настройки для конвертации видео для iPhone, iPad, Samsung, планшетов Android, фаблетов, smart телевизоров и смартфонов. Используйте режим пакетного преобразования для одновременного конвертирования большого количества файлов.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Конвертируйте видео между всеми ключевыми форматами с помощью Free AVS Video Converter абсолютно бесплатно: MP4, DVD, MPEG, VOB, 2K QHD, 4K UHD, MOV, AVI, WMV, MKV, FLV, TS, Blu-ray и т. Д. Используйте умные пресеты, чтобы конвертировать видео для iPhone, iPad, Samsung, планшетов Android, фаблетов, smart телевизоров и смартфонов. 
Free AVS Video Converter позволяет конвертировать HD, Full HD, 2K Quad HD, 4K Ultra HD и DCI 4K видео с использованием ультра новых пресетов и наслаждаться высококачественным воспроизведением видео. 
Конвертируйте видео файлы, включая MKV с субтитрами, легко и быстро. 
Free AVS Video Converter может ускорить конвертацию видео несколькими способами. Вы можете конвертировать большое количество видеофайлов одновременно, выбирая пакетную конвертацию или режимы командной строки. Режим командной строки помогает автоматизировать и планировать процесс конвертации, что чрезвычайно полезно для рутинной работы. 
Используйте аппаратное ускорение для декодирования видео с помощью видеокарт (GPU): Intel HD Graphics (технология Intel® Quick Sync Video) или NVIDIA® GeForce® (платформа NVIDIA CUDA®). Эти технологии помогают воспроизводить и конвертировать видео Full HD с высокой скоростью передачи данных или 2K QHD и 4K UHD быстрее. 
Вносите основные изменения перед конвертацией видео: корректируйте соотношение сторон, масштаб изображения, разделяйте видео по размеру или разделам, экспортируйте аудио и изображения из видео, добавляйте различные видео, аудио и текстовые эффекты. Экспериментируйте с новыми эффектами, такими как стрелки, Tilt-shift, частицы, обратный отсчет и т.д. 
Конвертируйте видео на YouTube бесплатно и быстро, выбирайте необходимые пресеты в зависимости от желаемого качества выходного файла. Free AVS Video Converter также конвертирует видео для Facebook и популярных видеохостингов, таких как Vimeo, Daily Motion, Telly. Записывайте DVD / Blu-ray диски со стильным меню.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </Russian>
    <Spanish>
      <Keywords>video converter, convertidor de vídeos, convertidor mp4, convertidor de video a mp3, convertir video a mp4, convertidor de videos gratis, convertir video a audio</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Convierta todos los formatos de vídeo gratis.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Convierta todos los formatos de vídeo con Free AVS Video Converter gratis.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Convierta vídeo a cualquier formato de video y para todos los dispositivos populares con Free AVS Video Converter. Convierta MP4 DVD AVI MPEG VOB MOV WMV M4V HDV gratis y rápidamente. Acelere la conversión de vídeo con GPU. Exporta audio desde vídeo.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Convierta vídeo entre todos los formatos con Free AVS Video Converter absolutamente gratis: MP4, DVD, MPEG, VOB, 2K QHD, 4K UHD, MOV, AVI, WMV, MKV, FLV, TS, Blu-ray, etc. Use presets inteligentes para convertir vídeos para iPhone, iPad, Samsung, tabletas Android, phablets, smart TV y smartphones. Convierta una gran cantidad de archivos de vídeo a la vez usando el modo de conversión por lotes. Grabe vídeo en discos DVD / Blu-ray con un menú.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Convierta vídeo entre todos los formatos con Free AVS Video Converter absolutamente gratis: MP4, DVD, MPEG, VOB, 2K QHD, 4K UHD, MOV, AVI, WMV, MKV, FLV, TS, Blu-ray, etc. Use presets inteligentes para convertir vídeos para iPhone, iPad, Samsung, tabletas Android, phablets, smart TV y smartphones. 
Free AVS Video Converter le permite convertir vídeos HD, Full HD, 2K Quad HD, 4K Ultra HD y DCI 4K usando presets ultra nuevos para que disfrute de una reproducción de video de alta calidad. 
Convierta archivos de vídeo incluyendo MKV con subtítulos de manera fácil y rápida. 
Free AVS Video Converter puede acelerar la conversión de video de varias maneras. Puede convertir una gran cantidad de archivos de vídeo a la vez, eligiendo la conversión por lotes o el modo de línea de comandos. El modo de línea de comandos ayuda a automatizar y programar la conversión que es extremadamente útil para el trabajo de rutina. 
Utilice la aceleración de hardware para la decodificación de vídeo mediante tarjetas de vídeo (GPU): Intel HD Graphics (tecnología Intel® Quick Sync Video) o NVIDIA® GeForce® (plataforma NVIDIA CUDA®). Estas tecnologías ayudan a reproducir y convertir vídeo Full HD con bitrate alto o 2K QHD y 4K UHD más rápido. 
Modifique vídeo antes de convertirlo: corrija la relación de aspecto, divida vídeo por tamaño o capítulos, exporte audio e imágenes de vídeo, agregue varios efectos de vídeo, audio y texto. Aplique nuevos efectos tales como flechas, Tilt-shift, partículas, cuenta atrás, etc. 
Convierta vídeo para YouTube de forma gratuita y rápida, seleccione un ajuste preestablecido según la calidad deseada del archivo de salida. Asimismo Free AVS Video Converter convierte vídeos para Facebook y sitios web de alojamiento de vídeos populares Vimeo, Daily Motion, Telly y otros. Grabe discos DVD / Blu-ray con menús elegantes.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </Spanish>
  </Program_Descriptions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
