<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
  <MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>4.0</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>RoboSoft 4.0.797</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>http://robosoft.rudenko.com</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR_URL>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
  </MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
  <RoboSoft>
    <Company_UIN>CMP-005B0BB0661</Company_UIN>
    <Company_Description></Company_Description>
    <Product_UIN>APP-00751CDEC8</Product_UIN>
    <Search_String>AVS Audio Editor</Search_String>
    <Search_String_Unique>AVS Audio Editor</Search_String_Unique>
    <Publish_on_CD>FALSE</Publish_on_CD>
    <RSProductType></RSProductType>
    <Press_Release_Search_String></Press_Release_Search_String>
    <NewsFeed_Search_String></NewsFeed_Search_String>
    <Search_Engine_Search_String></Search_Engine_Search_String>
    <Web_Directories_Search_String></Web_Directories_Search_String>
    <Comments_For_Reviewer></Comments_For_Reviewer>
    <Backlink></Backlink>
  </RoboSoft>
  <Company_Info>
    <Company_Name>Online Media Technologies Ltd., UK</Company_Name>
    <Address_1>Suite 12, 2nd Floor, Queens House</Address_1>
    <Address_2>180 Tottenham Court Road</Address_2>
    <City_Town>London</City_Town>
    <State_Province></State_Province>
    <Zip_Postal_Code>W1T 7PD</Zip_Postal_Code>
    <Country>United Kingdom</Country>
    <Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.avs4you.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
    <Contact_Info>
      <Contact_First_Name>Irina</Contact_First_Name>
      <Contact_Last_Name>Sanaeva</Contact_Last_Name>
      <Contact_Email>submit@avs4you.com</Contact_Email>
      <Author_First_Name>Irina</Author_First_Name>
      <Author_Last_Name>Sanaeva</Author_Last_Name>
      <Author_Email>submit@avs4you.com</Author_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
    <Support_Info>
      <Sales_Email>submit@avs4you.com</Sales_Email>
      <Support_Email>submit@avs4you.com</Support_Email>
      <General_Email>submit@avs4you.com</General_Email>
      <Sales_Phone></Sales_Phone>
      <Support_Phone></Support_Phone>
      <General_Phone></General_Phone>
      <Fax_Phone></Fax_Phone>
    </Support_Info>
    <GooglePlusPage></GooglePlusPage>
    <LinkedinPage></LinkedinPage>
    <TwitterCompanyPage>https://twitter.com/avs4you</TwitterCompanyPage>
    <FacebookCompanyPage>https://www.facebook.com/avs4you</FacebookCompanyPage>
    <CompanyStorePage></CompanyStorePage>
  </Company_Info>
  <ASP>
    <ASP_FORM>Y</ASP_FORM>
    <ASP_Member>Y</ASP_Member>
    <ASP_Member_Number>06467</ASP_Member_Number>
  </ASP>
  <NewsFeed>
    <NewsFeed_FORM>Y</NewsFeed_FORM>
    <NewsFeed_VERSION>1.0</NewsFeed_VERSION>
    <NewsFeed_URL>http://Submit-Everywhere.com/extensions/NewsFeed.htm</NewsFeed_URL>
    <NewsFeed_DESCRIPTION>This PAD extension allows you to add your RSS and Atom news feeds info into your PAD file. This info can be used by RSS feed submission software or by feed directories themselves.</NewsFeed_DESCRIPTION>
    <NewsFeed_Type>RSS 0.90</NewsFeed_Type>
    <NewsFeed_Language>English</NewsFeed_Language>
    <NewsFeed_Purpose>News</NewsFeed_Purpose>
    <NewsFeed_Author_Email>submit@avs4you.com</NewsFeed_Author_Email>
    <NewsFeed_Author_First_Name>Irina</NewsFeed_Author_First_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Author_Last_Name>Sanaeva</NewsFeed_Author_Last_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Feed_URL></NewsFeed_Feed_URL>
    <NewsFeed_Site_Name></NewsFeed_Site_Name>
    <NewsFeed_Site_URL></NewsFeed_Site_URL>
    <NewsFeed_Title></NewsFeed_Title>
    <NewsFeed_Description_70></NewsFeed_Description_70>
    <NewsFeed_Description_250></NewsFeed_Description_250>
  </NewsFeed>
  <PAD_Certification_Promotion>
    <Apply_For_Certification>N</Apply_For_Certification>
  </PAD_Certification_Promotion>
  <Program_Info>
    <File_Info>
      <Automatically_Detect_File_Size>N</Automatically_Detect_File_Size>
      <File_Size_Bytes>50527232</File_Size_Bytes>
      <File_Size_K>49343</File_Size_K>
      <File_Size_MB>48.19</File_Size_MB>
      <Filename_Versioned></Filename_Versioned>
      <Filename_Previous></Filename_Previous>
      <Filename_Generic></Filename_Generic>
      <Filename_Long></Filename_Long>
    </File_Info>
    <Program_Target_Platform>Windows</Program_Target_Platform>
    <Program_Name>AVS Audio Editor</Program_Name>
    <Program_Version>10.0.4.553</Program_Version>
    <Program_Release_Month>12</Program_Release_Month>
    <Program_Release_Day>11</Program_Release_Day>
    <Program_Release_Year>2020</Program_Release_Year>
    <Program_Cost_Dollars>39</Program_Cost_Dollars>
    <Program_Type>Shareware</Program_Type>
    <Program_Release_Status>New Release</Program_Release_Status>
    <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
    <Program_OS_Support>Win2000,WinXP,Win7 x32,Win7 x64,Windows 8,Windows 10,WinServer,WinOther,Windows2000,Windows2003,Windows Server 2000,Windows Server 2003,Windows Server 2008,Windows Server 2008r2,Windows Server 2012,Windows Tablet PC Edition 2005,Windows Media Center Edition 2005,WinVista,Windows Vista Starter,Windows Vista Home Basic,Windows Vista Home Premium,Windows Vista Business,Windows Vista Enterprise,Windows Vista Ultimate,WinVista x64,Windows Vista Home Basic x64,Windows Vista Home Premium x64,Windows Vista Business x64,Windows Vista Enterprise x64,Windows Vista Ultimate x64</Program_OS_Support>
    <Program_Language>English,Dutch,French,German,Italian,Japanese,Polish,Russian,Spanish</Program_Language>
    <Program_Change_Info>Support of M4A dash audio &amp; MP4 dash video. Some bug fixes</Program_Change_Info>
    <Program_System_Requirements>Intel/AMD compatible CPU at 1.86 GHz, 1 GB RAM, sound card, DirectX 9.0c</Program_System_Requirements>
    <Program_Category_Class>Audio &amp; Multimedia::Music Composers</Program_Category_Class>
    <Expire_Info>
      <Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
      <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
      <Expire_Count></Expire_Count>
      <Expire_Other_Info></Expire_Other_Info>
      <Expire_Month></Expire_Month>
      <Expire_Day></Expire_Day>
      <Expire_Year></Expire_Year>
    </Expire_Info>
    <Program_Categories>Audio Recorders,Audio Editors,Music Composers,Audio,Multimedia</Program_Categories>
    <Limitations>Voice logo on the output files</Limitations>
    <Program_Cost_Other_Code></Program_Cost_Other_Code>
    <Program_Cost_Other></Program_Cost_Other>
    <Awards></Awards>
    <Program_Specific_Category></Program_Specific_Category>
    <Includes_JAVA_VM></Includes_JAVA_VM>
    <Includes_VB_Runtime></Includes_VB_Runtime>
    <Includes_DirectX></Includes_DirectX>
    <FacebookProductPage></FacebookProductPage>
    <GooglePlusProductPage></GooglePlusProductPage>
  </Program_Info>
  <Dynamic_PAD>
    <Dynamic_Distributive>N</Dynamic_Distributive>
  </Dynamic_PAD>
  <Web_Info>
    <Application_URLs>
      <Application_Info_URL>https://www.avs4you.com/avs-audio-editor.aspx</Application_Info_URL>
      <Application_Order_URL>http://www.avs4you.com/register.aspx</Application_Order_URL>
      <Application_Screenshot_URL>http://www.avs4you.com/pads/screenshots/avsaudioeditor.jpg</Application_Screenshot_URL>
      <Application_Icon_URL>http://www.avs4you.com/pads/icons/avsaudioeditor.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
      <Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.avs4you.com/pads/en/avsaudioeditor.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
    <Download_URLs>
      <Primary_Download_URL>http://download.avs4you.com/distributives/AVSAudioEditor.exe</Primary_Download_URL>
      <Secondary_Download_URL></Secondary_Download_URL>
      <Additional_Download_URL_1></Additional_Download_URL_1>
      <Additional_Download_URL_2></Additional_Download_URL_2>
    </Download_URLs>
  </Web_Info>
  <Permissions>
    <Distribution_Permissions>This product can be freely distributed through the Internet. To publish it on a CD, please contact info@avs4you.com.</Distribution_Permissions>
    <EULA>END-USER LICENSE AGREEMENT FOR SOFTWARE PRODUCTS OF ONLINE MEDIA TECHNOLOGIES LTD.

IMPORTANT-READ CAREFULLY: This End-User License Agreement is a legal Agreement between you and Online Media Technologies Ltd for the applicable Software Products of Online Media Technologies Ltd. Do not copy, install, or use the Software Products provided under this license agreement ("Agreement"), until you have carefully read the following terms and conditions.

Any reproduction or redistribution of Software Products or any of its components not in accordance with the End-User License Agreement is expressly prohibited by law, and may result in severe civil and criminal penalties. 

Definitions: Software Products shall mean and include AVS4YOU Software. 

AVS4YOU Software shall mean all of the contents of the files (provided either by electronic download, on physical media or any other method of distribution), disk(s), CD-ROM(s) or other media with which this Agreement is provided) which may be found at www.avs4you.com. 

AVS4YOU Software is licensed on a per computer basis. Each license purchased is bound to one particular computer and allows using AVS4YOU Software on that single computer. If you install and use or reinstall AVS4YOU software on any other computers you will have to purchase an additional license for each computer. If you change a computer, you will have to purchase an additional license. All updates and upgrades for AVS4YOU Software are free for a user throughout the period of AVS4YOU license validity. 

Your rights and obligations with respect to the use of AVS4YOU Software or any of its components are as follows: 

You may: 
1. Install and use one copy of AVS4YOU Software or any of its components and all upgrades and updates on a single computer for any period for which you have purchased a subscription (typically 1 year or Unlimited). 
2. Make one copy of AVS4YOU Software or any of its components for archival purposes on a storage device or media. 
3. Use AVS4YOU Software on a network, provided that you have a licensed copy of AVS4YOU Software for each computer that can access AVS4YOU Software over that network for any period for which you have purchased a subscription (typically 1 year or Unlimited). A license for AVS4YOU Software may not be shared or used concurrently on different computers. 
4. Receive support by e-mail to answer questions and solve problems referred to AVS4YOU Software for any period for which you have purchased a subscription (typically 1 year or Unlimited). 

You may not: 
1. Use, copy, modify, or transfer copies of AVS4YOU Software except as provided for in this License. 
2. Remove any proprietary notices or labels from AVS4YOU Software. 
3. Reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble or make derivative works based on AVS4YOU Software (except and only to the extent that such activity is expressly permitted by applicable law notwithstanding this limitation). 
4. Rent, lease, sublicense or assign AVS4YOU Software or any copy thereof, including any related documentation. 
5. Separate AVS4YOU Software component parts for use on more than one computer. 
6. Distribute the license key in any way. 
7. Make any attempt to discover the source code of AVS4YOU Software. 


NO WARRANTIES. 

Online Media Technologies Ltd. expressly disclaims any warranty for AVS4YOU Software. 

AVS4YOU SOFTWARE AND ANY RELATED DOCUMENTATION is PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NONINFRINGEMENT. 

THE ENTIRE RISK ARISING OUT OF USE OR PERFORMANCE OF AVS4YOU SOFTWARE REMAINS WITH YOU. 

NO LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES. 
IN NO EVENT SHALL ONLINE MEDIA TECHNOLOGIES LTD BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF BUSINESS PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, LOSS OF BUSINESS INFORMATION, OR ANY OTHER PECUNIARY LOSS) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OR OF INABILITY TO USE AVS4YOU SOFTWARE. 

COPYRIGHT NOTICE. Copyright(C) 2020 Online Media Technologies Ltd. All rights reserved. 
Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.</EULA>
  </Permissions>
  <AppStore>
    <AppStore_AppID></AppStore_AppID>
    <AppStore_Category></AppStore_Category>
    <AppStore_Info_URL></AppStore_Info_URL>
    <AppStore_Download_URL></AppStore_Download_URL>
    <AppStore_Promo_Code_1></AppStore_Promo_Code_1>
    <AppStore_Promo_Code_2></AppStore_Promo_Code_2>
    <AppStore_Promo_Code_3></AppStore_Promo_Code_3>
    <AppStore_Supported_Devices></AppStore_Supported_Devices>
    <AppStore_Other_Applications></AppStore_Other_Applications>
    <AppStore_Advantages_And_Unique_Features></AppStore_Advantages_And_Unique_Features>
    <AppStore_Awards_And_Ratings></AppStore_Awards_And_Ratings>
  </AppStore>
  <Program_Descriptions>
    <English>
      <Keywords>MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, OGG, song editor, recording editor, voice recording, record audio, song cutter and joiner, split audio file, create ringtone, mix songs, audiograbber, cd ripper, audio mix, mixing audio, remove noise, noise removal</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>A perfect and easy tool to edit your audio.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Edit your audio collection with AVS Audio Editor.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Edit your audio collection, record audio data and create unique ringtones for iPhone. Remove background noises. Apply effects. Edit and save audio files in MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A,WMA, AAC, MP2, AMR, OGG,etc. Edit audio directly in your video recordings.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Cut, join, trim, mix, delete parts, split with AVS Audio Editor. Manage your tracks in MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, MP2, AMR, OGG, etc. Record audio data from various inputs like microphone, vinyl records, and other input lines. Create a unique ringtone for iPhone. AVS Audio Editor is a part of the AVS4YOU.com package. Register once at avs4you.com and work with all tools from the AVS4YOU.com package. Subscribe for $39/year or $59/lifetime.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>AVS Audio Editor is a perfect tool for audio editing. Edit and save audio files in MP3, WMA, WAV, FLAC, M4A, AAC, AMR, OGG, AC3 etc. 
Cut, join, trim, mix, delete parts, split audio with AVS Audio Editor. 
Record audio data from various inputs like microphone, vinyl records, and other input lines on a sound card. 
Extract and edit audio from your video files directly in the program interface. 
Improve sound quality using specially designed filters to remove noise and irritating sounds like roaring, hissing, crackling, etc. 
Select between 20 built-in effects including delay, flanger, equalizer, chorus, reverb, auto correction and more. 
Mix audio and blend several audio tracks. 
Edit an audio track and create your own ringtone for iPhone. Work faster - make up a Favourites panel with the most frequently used functions. 
Text to Speech allows to convert any written text into a natural sounding voice with a single click. Save it in a popular audio format that can be played on any device. Speed up or slow the speech rate down, change pitch if necessary. 
AVS Audio Editor is a part of the AVS4YOU package. Register once and work with all tools from the AVS4YOU.com. Subscribe for $39/year or $59/lifetime.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </English>
    <German>
      <Keywords>audio editor, audio bearbeiten, music mixer, audioaufnahme, wma, mp3, ogg, pcm, wav, aiff, au, m4a, flac, aac, amr, audio mixen, Rauschen entfernen, lieder zusammenschneiden, internetradio aufnehmen, stereomix, musik mitschneiden, mp3 zuschneiden</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Ein perfektes Tool für Audiobearbeitung.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Ihre Audiosammlung mit AVS Audio Editor bearbeiten.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Ihre Audiosammlung bearbeiten, Audiodaten aufnehmen, Hintergrund Rauschen dämpfen. Effekte anwenden. Audio in MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, OGG usw. bearbeiten. Klingeltöne für iPhone erstellen. Audio direkt in Ihren Videos bearbeiten.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Bearbeiten, schneiden, aufnehmen, verbessern, Effekte und Filter anwenden. Bearbeiten Sie Audio in MP3, M4A/M4R, FLAC, SHN, APE, VOC, MIDI, usw. mit AVS Audio Editor. Ärgerliche Geräusche enfernen. Audio direkt in Ihren Video Aufnahmen bearbeiten. Eigene Klingeltöne für iPhone erstellen. Erwerben Sie käuflich ein Abonnement für €39/Jahr oder €49/unbefristet und benutzen Sie alle Anwendungen aus dem AVS4YOU.com-Paket.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Um einen Hit zu erstellen, braucht man keine professionellen Kenntnisse zu haben! AVS Audio Editor ist perfekt für Audiobearbeitung. 
Bearbeiten und speichern Sie Audiodateien in MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, MP2, AMR, OGG usw. mit dem AVS Audio Editor. 
Schneiden, vereinigen, mixen, löschen Sie unerwünschte Abschnitte, teilen Sie Audiodateien mit dem AVS Audio Editor auf. Verwenden Sie die Zeitachse für maximale Genauigkeit. 
Nutzen Sie speziell entwickelte Filter zum Entfernen des Rauschens aller Art. Wählen Sie unter 20 eingebauten Effekten und Filtern wie Delay, Flanger, Chorus, Nachhall und anderen. 
Mischen Sie mehrere Audiotracks. Nehmen Sie Audiodaten aus unterschiedlichen Quellen wie aus einem Mikrofon, einer Schallplatte oder einem anderen Eingang Ihrer Soundkarte auf. Bearbeiten Sie aufgezeichnete Audiodaten, wenden Sie Effekte an, speichern Sie Audiodateien in eines der unterstützten Formate ab. 
Exportieren und bearbeiten Sie Audiospuren aus Ihren Videodateien mit dem AVS Audio Editor. Speichern Sie diese auf dem PC oder einem externen Gerät. 
Wenden Sie Batch-Modus, um einige Einstellungen auf mehrere Audiodateien anzuwenden. 
Bearbeiten Sie eine Audiodatei und speichern Sie diese ins M4R-Format für Ihr iPhone. Erstellen Sie einen einzigartigen Klingelton mit dem AVS Audio Editor. 
Erstellen Sie Ihre Favoritenleiste mit am häufigsten verwendeten Funktionen des Programms und fügen Sie zu dieser Leiste hinzu. 
AVS Audio Editor ist ein Bestandteil des AVS4YOU.com-Pakets. Registrieren Sie sich einmal auf der Website avs4you.com und benutzen Sie alle Anwendungen aus dem AVS4YOU.com-Paket. Erwerben Sie käuflich ein Abonnement für €39/Jahr oder €49/unbefristet. 
Die AVS4YOU-Programme ermöglichen Ihnen Audio- und Videodateien zu rippen, zu konvertieren und zu bearbeiten, DVDs zu brennen, Klingeltöne zu erstellen, Videos auf tragbare Geräte, Player sowie Mobiltelefone zu übertragen und vieles mehr!</Char_Desc_2000>
    </German>
    <French>
      <Keywords>MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, OGG, éditeur audio, enregistrement vocal, enregistrement audio, couper des chansons, mixer de la musique, audiograbber, cd ripper, mix audio, éliminer le bruit, suppresion du bruit</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Un outil facile pour éditer fichiers audio.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Éditez votre collection audio avec AVS Audio Editor.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Éditez la collection audio, enregistrez les données audio,créez des sonneries pour iPhone. Eliminez le bruit de fond.Appliquez des effets. Éditez,sauvegardez l'audio aux formats MP3,FLAC,WAV,M4A,WMA,AAC, etc. Éditez l'audio des enregistrements vidéo.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Éditez, fractionnez,coupez,découpez,appliquez des effets et des filtres. Gérez les pistes MP3,FLAC,WAV,M4A,WMA,AAC, etc. avec AVS Audio Editor. Enregistrez des données audio de diverses entrées:microphone, disques vinyles etc.Créez une sonnerie pour iPhone.AVS Audio Editor fait partie de l'ensemble des logiciels AVS4YOU. Inscrivez-vous pour €39/abonnement à 1 an ou €49/abonnement illimité et utilisez tous les logiciels du site avs4you.com.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Gérez vos fichiers audio en utilisant une large gamme des outils faciles d'emploi. 
AVS Audio Editor est un outil idéal pour éditer de l'audio. Éditez et sauvegardez des fichiers audio aux formats MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, MP2, AMR, OGG, etc. avec AVS Audio Editor. 
Coupez, mixez, découpez, supprimez des parties, fractionnez avec AVS Audio Editor. 
Utilisez les filtres spécialement conçus pour éliminer des bruits, des sifflements, des craquements etc. 
Appliquez plus de 20 effets et filtres tels que retard, flanger, chorus, réverbération et d'autres. 
Mixage audio et mélange de plusieurs pistes audio. Enregistrez les données audio à partir des sources différentes, telles que microphone, disques de vinyle, et d'autres entrées de votre carte son. 
Extraction de l'audio des vidéos. Modifiez des enregistrements audio, appliquez des effets, sélectionnez le format de sauvegarde désiré. 
Traitement par lots: application des paramètres prédéfinis à plusieurs fichiers en une seule fois. Application du filtre de la réduction de bruit. 
Éditez une piste audio et créez votre propre sonnerie pour iPhone. 
Travaillez plus vite - créez un groupe des favoris des fonctions fréquemment utilisées. 
AVS Audio Editor fait partie de l'ensemble des logiciels AVS4YOU. Inscrivez-vous sur le site avs4you.com et utilisez tous les outils de l'ensemble des logiciels du site. Inscrivez-vous pour €39/abonnement à 1 an ou pour €49/abonnement illimité. 
Les logiciels AVS4YOU vous permettent d'extraire, de convertir et d'éditer des fichiers audio/vidéo facilement, de graver DVD, de créer des sonneries, de télécharger des vidéos sur les appareils portables, lecteurs, téléphones et encore plus !</Char_Desc_2000>
    </French>
    <Russian>
      <Keywords>редактор песен, аудио редактор, редактор музыки, музыкальный редактор, запись звука, программа для записи, запись голоса, нарезка музыки, создать рингтон, микширование звука, удаление шума, audiograber, cd grabber, MP3,FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Удобный инструмент для редактирования аудио.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Редактируйте Вашу коллекцию аудиофайлов с помощью AVS Audio Editor.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Редактируйте аудиофайлы, записывайте звуковые данные с различных источников, создайте оригинальный рингтон для iPhone. Редактируйте и сохраняйте аудиофайлы в форматы MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, MP2, AMR, OGG и др. с AVS Audio Editor.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Вырезайте, объединяйте, обрезайте, микшируйте, удаляйте части, разделяйте файлы с помощью программы AVS Audio Editor. AVS Audio Editor позволяет редактировать и сохранять аудиофайлы в форматы MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, MP2, AMR, OGG и другие. Записывайте звуковые данные с различных источников: с микрофона, виниловых пластинок и других входов звуковой карты. Создайте свой собственный оригинальный рингтон с помощью программы AVS Audio Editor.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Audio Editor располагает широким спектром инструментов для редактирования даудиофайлов. 
Редактируйте и сохраняйте аудиофайлы в форматы MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, MP2, AMR, OGG и другие с помощью программы AVS Audio Editor. 
Вырезайте, объединяйте, обрезайте, микшируйте, удаляйте части, разделяйте файлы. 
Применяйте специально разработанные фильтры, чтобы удалить раздражающие звуки, такие как свист, шипение, треск и другие. 
Выбирайте любой из 20 встроенных эффектов и фильтров - в их числе задержка, флэнжер, хорус, реверберация и другие. Микшируйте звук, смешивая несколько дорожек. 
При помощи AVS Audio Editor Вы можете записывать звуковые данные с различных источников: с микрофона, виниловых пластинок и других входов звуковой карты. 
Извлекайте и редактируйте звуковые дорожки из своих видеофайлов с помощью AVS Audio Editor. Сохраняйте их на компьютере или на внешнем носителе. 
Используйте пакетное редактирование для обработки нескольких аудиофайлов одновременно. Отредактируйте аудиофайл и сохраните его в формат M4R для iPhone. Создайте свой собственный оригинальный рингтон с помощью программы AVS Audio Editor. 
AVS Audio Editor является частью пакета AVS4YOU.com. На сайте www.avs4you.com Вы можете приобрести одногодичную подписку за 1999 руб. или безлимитную подписку за 2499 руб. 
AVS4YOU продукты позволяют легко конвертировать и редактировать аудио/видео файлы, редактировать изображения, записывать DVD, создавать рингтоны, загружать видео на портативные устройства, плееры, телефоны и многое другое!</Char_Desc_2000>
    </Russian>
    <Spanish>
      <Keywords>MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, OGG, editor de canciones, editor de grabaciones, grabación de voz, grabación de audio, dividir audio, crear tonos de llamada, mezclar canciones, audiograbber, cd ripper, mezclar audios, eliminación de ruido</Keywords>
      <Char_Desc_45>Herramienta perfecta para editar su audio.</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Edite su colección de audio con AVS Audio Editor.</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Edite su colección de audio, grabe datos de audio y cree tonos de llamada únicos. Elimine ruidos de fondo. Aplique effectos. Edite y guarde archivos de audio en MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, OGG, etc.Edite audio directamente en sus grabaciones de vídeo.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Edite, recorte, grabe, divida, aplique efectos y filtros. Administre sus pistas en MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, OGG etc. Grabe datos de audio de varias entradas como micrófono, discos de vinilo y otras líneas de entrada. Cree tono de llamada único. AVS Audio Editor es una parte del paquete AVS4YOU.com. Regístrese una vez en avs4you.com y trabaje con todas las herramientas del paquete AVS4YOU.com. Suscríbase por €39/año o €49/por vida.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Administre sus archivos de audio utilizando una amplia gama de herramientas útiles. 
AVS Audio Editor es una herramienta perfecta para la edición de audio. Edite y guarde archivos de audio en MP3, FLAC, WAV, M4A, WMA, AAC, MP2, AMR, OGG, etc. con AVS Audio Editor. 
Corte, una, recorte, mezcle, elimine partes, divida con AVS Audio Editor. 
Utilice filtros especialmente diseñados para eliminar sonidos irritantes como rugido, siseo, chicharrones etc. 
Seleccione entre 20 efectos y filtros integrados, incluyendo retardo, flanger, coro, reverberación, corrección automática y más. 
Mezcle audio y varias pistas de audio. Grabe los datos de audio de varias entradas como micrófono, discos de vinilo y otras líneas de entrada en una tarjeta de sonido. 
Exporte audio desde video. Edite pistas de audio y guárdelas en cualquier formato de audio. Utilice edición por lotes para aplicar determinadas configuraciones a varios archivos de una sola vez. 
Suavice silbidos no deseados con filtros de reducción de ruido. Edite pista de audio y cree su propio tono de llamada para iPhone. 
Trabaje más rápido: componga un panel de Favoritos con las funciones más utilizadas. 
AVS Audio Editor es una parte del paquete AVS4YOU. Regístrese una vez en avs4you.com y trabaje con todas las herramientas del paquete AVS4YOU.com. Suscríbase por € 39/año o € 49/por vida. 
¡Las herramientas AVS4YOU le permiten extraer, convertir y editar fácilmente archivos de audio/video, grabar DVDs, crear tonos de llamada, subir vídeos a dispositivos portátiles, reproductores, teléfonos y mucho más.</Char_Desc_2000>
    </Spanish>
  </Program_Descriptions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
